<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
	id="skin.kover"
	version="1.1.2"
	name="KOver"
	provider-name="Jayz2K">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.10.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.6.5" />
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.40"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.30"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1.00" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="16x9" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de_DE">K0ver [Kodi Overlay]. Ein anpassbarer Skin. Bau deine eigenen Ansichten und Farbeinstellungen.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. A customizable skin. Build your own views and color sets.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. A customisable skin. Build your own views and colour sets.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. A customizable skin. Build your own views and color sets.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Una skin personalizable. Construye tus propias vistas y tus paletas de colores.</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Muokattava ulkoasu. Luo omat näkymät ja väriteemat.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Un habillage personnalisable. Constuisez vos propres vues et palettes de couleurs.</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Una skin personalizzabile. Costruisci le tue viste e set di colori.</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Pritaikoma pagal poreikius teminė išvaizda. Susikurkite savus rodinius ir spalvų rinkinius.</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Satu kulit bolehsuai. Bina paparan dan set warna anda sendiri.</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">KOver [Nakładka na Kodi]. Skóra w pełni konfigurowalna. Stwórz swoje własne widoki i motywy kolorów.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Uma skin customizável. Construa seus modos de visualização e defina cores.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Izmenjljiva maska. Podesite sopstvene prikaze i skupove boja.</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">KOver (for KODI Overlay) offers a different approach of KODI skins. Not just purely designed, it also offers to the user the possibility to customize it and make thousands of configurations. KOver embeds two powerful WYSIWYG editors : The Designer and the Color tool. Move, resize, change content and colors ... make it yours !</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">KOver (for KODI Overlay) offers a different approach of KODI skins. Not just purely designed, it also offers to the user the possibility to customise it and make thousands of configurations. KOver embeds two powerful WYSIWYG editors : The Designer and the Colour tool. Move, resize, change content and colours ... make it yours !</description>
		<description lang="en_US">KOver (for KODI Overlay) offers a different approach of KODI skins. Not just purely designed, it also offers to the user the possibility to customize it and make thousands of configurations. KOver embeds two powerful WYSIWYG editors : The Designer and the Color tool. Move, resize, change content and colors ... make it yours !</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">KOver (de Kodi Overlay) ofrece una aproximación distinta a las skins de Kodi. No está estrictamente diseñada, sino que ofrece al usuario la posibilidad de personalizarla y hacer miles de configuraciones. KOver integra dos poderosos editores WYSIWYG: El Diseñador y la herramienta de Color. Mover, cambiar de tamaño, de color, de contenido... ¡Cómo quieras!</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">KOver (KODI Overlay) tarjoaa erilaisen lähestymistavan KODIn ulkoasuihin. Se antaa käyttäjälle mahdoillisuuden muokata käyttöliittymää tuhansilla eri tavoilla. KOverin mukana tulee kaksi monipuolista WYSIWYG-editoria: suunnittelutyökalu ja värityökalu. Siirrä, muuta kokoa, muokkaa sisältöä ja värejä... Tee siitä omanlaisesi!</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">KOver (pour KODI Overlay) offre une approche différente des habillages KODI. Plus qu'un simple habillage, les utilisateurs peuvent entièrement modifier son apparence et créer des milliers de configurations. KOver intègre deux éditeurs graphiques puissants : le Designer et l'Éditeur de couleurs. Déplacez, redimensionnez, changez les contenus et les couleurs ... faites-en votre habillage !</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">KOver (da KODI Overlay) offre un diverso approccio per le skin di KODI. Non solo puramente progettata, offre anche all'utente la possibilità di personalizzare e fare migliaia di configurazioni. KOver incorpora due potenti editor WYSIWYG: lo strumento Designer e quello Colore. Sposta, ridimensiona, cambia contenuto e colori... rendila tua!</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">KOver (KODI Overlay) siūlo kitokį požiūrį į KODI temines išvizdas. Ne tik skaidriai sukurta, bet ir siūlo vartotojui galimybę pritaikyti pagal savo poreikius suteikiant tūkstančius galimų konfigūracijų. KOver turi du galingus WYSIWYG redaktorius: dizainerį ir spalvų įrankį. Perkelkite, pakeiskite dydį, pakeiskite turinį ir spalvas ... susikurkite savo!</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">KOver (untuk Tindihan Atas KODI) menyediakan pelbagai pendekatan untuk kulit KODI. Bukan sahaja semata-mata direka, ia juga menawarkan keupayaan menyuai dan menghasilkan beribu-ribu konfigurasi. KOver membenamkan dua penyunting WYSIWYG yang hebat : Pereka dan alat Warna. Alih, saiz semula, ubah kandungan dan warna ... jadikan kulit tersebut hasil ciptaan anda !</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Kover (para KODI Overlay) oferece uma abordagem diferente das demais skins para Kodi. Não apenas puramente projetada, mas também oferece ao usuário a possibilidade de personalizá-lo e fazer milhares de configurações. Kover incorpora dois poderosos editores WYSIWYG: O Designer e a ferramenta Color. Mova, redimensione, altere conteúdos e cores ... Faça você mesmo!</description>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Ползването на мишка и чуствителни на допир монитори не се поддържа</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Maus und Touch-Geräte werden nicht unterstützt</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Mouse and Touch device not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Mouse and Touch device not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Mouse and Touch device not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">No se soporta ratón ni táctil</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Hiiren tai kosketusnäytön käyttöä ei tueta</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Souris et appareils tactiles non pris en charge</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">אין תמיכה בעכבר או מסכי מגע</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Mouse e dispositivi Touch non supportati</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Pelė ir liečiamieji įrenginiai nepalaikomi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Peranti Tetikus dan Sentuh tidak disokong</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Brak obsługi myszy i urządzeń dotykowych</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Sem suporte a mouse e disposítivos de toque </disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Mausul și dispozitivul cu ecran tactil nu sunt sprijinite</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Miš i Table na dodir nisu podržane</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=252</forum>
		<website>https://plus.google.com/communities/101384208271707123426</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/Jayz2K/skin.KOver</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
